Santiago Dziencielsky

Account Manager

E: santidzi@qmail.com LI: linkedin.com/santidzi T: 646-483-0764

Bilingual (English-Spanish) account manager with 6 years of experience in business development and client relations. Brings experience from a variety of industries, including financial services, importation and wholesale distribution, and HVAC.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Manager of Sales Operations, Ecoklima | June 2016 - March 2020 | Buenos Aires, Argentina

- Drive sales to commercial and retail customers and manage existing client relationships
- Create and implement innovative multi-channel strategies to generate leads and new business
 - Develop marketing campaigns via social media (Facebook and Instagram), email (MailChimp and Sendinblue) and Google Ads
 - Conduct email campaigns that reach 70,000 potential and existing customers monthly
 - Sell up to \$115,000+ per month to formerly cold prospects
- Analyze sales trends, prepare budgets, and research brands and products with attention to price and quality to create product catalog each fiscal year
- Manage relationships with key accounts by understanding their needs, maintaining a knowledge
 of products and solutions and treating each client with a personalized approach
- Grew revenue from \$1,704,397 in 2016 to \$2,207,659 in 2019 in collaboration with supervisor, a 29.5% increase

Lead Account Manager, Comercial Alpaca | May 2014 - June 2016 | Buenos Aires, Argentina

- Generated commercial and retail revenue and build long term relationships with existing and new accounts.
- Promoted new products to customer base and notified customers of upcoming shipments of frequently purchased items; negotiated prices and volume discounts
- Responsible for online sales via <u>MercadoLibre</u> and company site including photographing new products, developing product descriptions, creating listings, and fielding inquiries
- Oversaw team of 9 including administrative staff and warehouse and shipping employees

Loan Officer, Grupo Puerto | February 2012 - May 2014 | Buenos Aires, Argentina

- Sold retail loans up to \$10,000 within existing client base and managed loan applications and repayment processes
- Utilized Salesforce to enable personalized, informed communication and to track deals
- Conducted in-person meetings with clients to finalize loan process and close deals

EDUCATION

2017 | Bachelor's Degree, Media Production | Universidad de Belgrano | Buenos Aires, Argentina
 2011 - 2013 | Coursework towards Bachelor's Degree, Sports Journalism | Universidad ETER